Magnus Jan Krynski Collection CPAA 91.17
Connecticut Polish American Archives
- “The Peace Movement and the Soviet Union” by Vladimir Bukovsky, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- German-American National Political Action Committee (GANPAC)- Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Zdzislaw Rurarz- Correspondence, resume, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- "Przyszlosc Polski - material do dyskusji Pomostu" by Zdzislaw M. Rurarz, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Republican Convention- Correspondence, articles, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- John David Fox / East West Roundtable- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Larry Goodwyn- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Notes for the meeting with politicians, [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Polish Economy 1982- Summarized report (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Linda Chavez, newly appointed as White House public liaison director- Correspondence, article, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- William von Raab- Commissioner of Custom, US Custom Service- Articles, remarks, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Correspondence- American Political Foundation/ George Agree, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Correspondence- Committee for the Survival of a Free Congress/ Paul Weyrich, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Actor's boycott correspondence, newsnotes on Soviet and East European Drama and Theatre, vol.3, no.1-2, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Correspondence- Edward Asner/ Support for Polish actors' boycott, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Polish writers under the Martial Law- clippings, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Correspondence-Susan Sontag, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- PEN American Center- Correspondence, newsletters, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Terry Sanford, Duke University President- Articles, correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Life during the Martial Law in Poland - Articles, contacts, addresses, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Committee in Support of Solidarity- Aid for Poland, list of interned, arrested, sentenced and their families, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- International Rescue Committee- Correspondence, list of recent immigrants needing assistance, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Human Rights in Poland- United Nations publication, correspondence, press statements, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Correspondence- Perspectives author Marta Korwin-Rhodes, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Helsinki Watch- Letter from prominent Americans to Wojciech Jaruzelski to release Solidarity activists, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- United Nations - Human Rights Commission, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- United Methodists for Liberty & Human Rights- Newsletter, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Poland 1983- “Report on Post-Martial law Legal Conditions” by Polish Independent Students Association and Polish Institute of Arts and Sciences (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Catholic Church in US and Poland and politics- Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Solidarity Sister City Program- Durham, N.C. & Bialystok- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, press statements, petitions- Max Kampelman (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Poland- Jokes, humor, cartoons, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Alice Catherine Carls, Sterling College- Correspondence, clippings, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- “Cardinal Glemp's Church” by Alice Catherine Carls, [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 44)
- “Poland's Roman Catholic Church Today” by Alice Catherine Carls, [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Peace Movement – Newspaper clippings, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- The Center for International Relations- Letter, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- The political left bias in media- Articles, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Nuclear Freeze- Clippings, articles, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Institute on Religion and Democracy- Newsletters, correspondence, notes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Congressional Directory listing, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Various mailing lists, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- National Conservative Political Action Committee- Correspondence, member documents, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Slave labor in USSR- Articles, Heritage Foundation Bulletin, press release, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Polish Independent Student's Association, New York- Letter, activity report, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- US Policy for Central America - White House Digest, memorandum, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Social Democrats, USA- Advertisements, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Democratic Socialists of America- Meeting announcements, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- International Monetary Fund- Clippings, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Lech Walesa- Nobel Prize- Interview in Playboy, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Addresses, [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Campus Coalition for Democracy - Duke University- Platform, newsletter, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Congressional campaign 1983- North Carolina Democrats (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Agreement with Polish Student in Lodz by Anna Sabbat- Radio Free Europe(RFE), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Solidarity materials at Wilson library, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- List of Polish newspapers in America, [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Young Americans for Freedom- Correspondence, articles, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Rabbi Alexander M. Schindler- 40th anniversary of Warsaw ghetto uprising- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Editorials regarding Poland, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Various newspaper articles, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Friends of Solidarity, Washington D.C.- Correspondence, annual report, Newsletter no.1-June 1982,no.2-Oct. 1982 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Republican Congressional campaign, N.C., 1982; 1984 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Corcoran resolution - HJ. Res 435 - Renouncing of Yalta, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Sawka Poster Orders, [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 74)
- The North American Study Center for Polish Affairs (STUDIUM)- Correspondence, news, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Mid East Information Resource - Newsletter July, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Biuletyn Prasowy: WiadomoSci ozyciu w Polsce, published by Free Europe, Inc. Jan. 1973-Nov. 1973 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Helsinki Watch reports, 1980; 1982 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Grants- How to guides, places to get funding, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Captive Nations Week- Correspondence, ceremony achedule, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Conference on the Security and Cooperation in Europe (CSCE), Madrid- Assessment, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- What is Radio Free Europe up to?- Firing Line program- Transcript, September 19, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- The College Republican National Committee, "Let the people go" project, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Freedom Federation- Voice Of America/Radio Free Europe- Budget requests, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- “Robotnicy 1980” [Polish documentary film]- Transcript of soundtrack [English translation], [n.d] (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Frontlash, Polish Workers' Task Force- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Accuracy in media reports, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Contentions published by The Committee for the Free World, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Press (The Committee for the Free World), 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 89)
- Measure published by University Centers for Rational Alternatives, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 90)
- Free Trade Union News, The American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1975-1984 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Addresses, business cards, etc., 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 92)
- “What do the Poles want?” By Leopold Tyrmand in Commentary, June, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- “Democracy for Everyone?” By Peter L. Berger, from Commentary, September 1983 (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Review of "The Interrogation" (Przesluchani) edited by Hilton Kramer in The New Criterion, October, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 95)
- “Business, Labor and Anti-Communist Struggle”, by Arch Puddington in The National Review, January, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Free Poland (Wolna Polska), September, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Smoloskyp newspaper (“A quarterly dealing with human rights affairs in Ukraine and Eastern Europe), Fall, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 98)
- “The Polish Press in America” by Jan Kowalik, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Clippings about Poland, Soviet bloc, American foreign policy, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Radio Free Europe (RFE)- Venice Biennale, [1964?] (Box 6, Folder 1)
- RFE- Ksiazka (Book Review), [1956-1963?] (Box 6, Folder 2)
- RFE- American Stage, part I, [1962-1964?] (Box 6, Folder 3)
- RFE- American Stage, part II, [1965-1967?] (Box 6, Folder 4)
- RFE New York Literary program, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- RFE NY Literary program, [1957-1960?] (Box 6, Folder 6)
- RFE NY Literary program, [1961-1963?] (Box 6, Folder 7)
- RFE NY Literary program, [1964-1966?] (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Kuznica, no. 9-12 (1950) negative (Box 6, Object 1)